#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/phuocbao-dung-nguyen-a643a0147 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Branding & Identity
Animation
User Flows

#### Certifications

Foundations of Project Management

## Phuoc Bao Dung Nguyen

**UI UX Designer** 

Vietnam

### Summary

I'm a multimedia designer with more than 6 years of experience in the UX / UI design industry with global clients such as Australia, America, France, and Vietnam.

-

Email: phuocbaodungnguyen@gmail.com

-

https://dribbble.com/dunli https://www.instagram.com/dunli.design https://www.behance.net/baodungnguyen

-

**Key Expertise** 

- UI / UX design
- Digital product design
- Design system
- UI kit creation
- Wireframing, Prototyping & Presentation
- Design research
- Illustration
- Implementation with developers

#### Tools & skills

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe After Effect
- Adobe Premiere Pro / Rush
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Lightroom
- Adobe Illustrator
- Blender

## Experience

Tenomad Company
Team Leader UI-UX Designer
February 2018 - Present (7 years 2 months)

Vietnam

- Manage a team of product designers focused on mobile, website and multi media design.
- Communicate regularly with project partners to gain alignment, resolve issues and articulate the business value of design activities.
- Coach product designers, guiding them along their career paths towards becoming strong cross-functional team members.
- Built User Flow, Screen Flow, Wireframes, Rapid and Hi-fi Prototype, Product Road-Map, Product Navigation System...
- Design and guide the exploration of a range of possibilities for the aesthetic vision of products/services
- Managed backlogs, prioritized features, defined MVP and Sprints of the product.
- Communicate regularly with project partners, website developers teams, and Mobile developers to reach a consensus, solve problems and find the best design for each function of the project

# Homing UI UX Design Lead February 2017 - Present (8 years 2 months)

California, United States

- As the product design leader, I am the liaison between the CEO of the project and the UI designers and developers.
- Communicate regularly with project partners, website developers teams, and Mobile developers to reach a consensus, solve problems and find the best design for each function of the project
- Built User Flow, Screen Flow, Wireframes, Rapid and Prototypes, and Road-Map for each function
- Manage a team of product designers focused on mobile, website, and multimedia design.
- Communicate product features, build final designs, and deliver to the development team.
- I built more marketing products, explainer videos, logo and branding products for the project.

MettaDepth UX Designer

#### February 2020 - Present (5 years 2 months)

California, United States

- Working with internal teams and clients from many different countries. Turn conceptual content into optimal finished designs
- Applied Design Thinking to design Features and Strategies for the product (User-Centered Approaching).
- Built User Flow, Screen Flow, Wireframes, Rapid and Prototype, Product Road-Map, Product Navigation System...
- Come together to come up with ideas for interaction design, animation with clients, design demos and deliverables, work with the development team to complete the design and product based on the idea concept,
- Handle the work of graphic design, marketing, videos and logos, branding.

Trip.Social

**UI** Designer

October 2018 - February 2021 (2 years 5 months)

Sydney, New South Wales, Australia

- · Trip.Social, formerly GoPavel
- Communicate regularly with teams, Worked with internal teams and stakeholders to generate ideas. from initial ideas to build up the most optimal designs.
- Work directly with the founder to analyze requirements, and ideas into design flow.
- Design UI for all features for mobile app and website
- Design and build brand identity including logo, mascot and digital products, advertising...

Inlumina

**UI** Designer

May 2017 - April 2018 (1 year)

Freepik Company

Graphic Illustrator

2015 - 2018 (3 years)

I create illustrated products, vector graphics about the logo, branding, UI... to sell them on freepik.

4Children Cartoon Team

**Animation Artist** 

February 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 8 months)

I create the characters, animate them according to the original script, and create funny animations for our studio, for young people all over the world.

## Education

Hue University – University of Arts
University bachelor, Multimedia Designer · (February 2011 - February 2016)